The repository “Both Expts comparison” contains the R analysis script and RT data for both experiments in 1 file.  The conditions are relabeled to congruent vs. incongruent to allow a comparison of the magnitude of the congruency effect across the two experiments.

The repository “Expt 1 Script and Data” contains the R analysis script for the Anger/Fear experiment, the RT data, the accuracy data and the two data files (containing the word “graph”) used by ggplot2 to graph the means and SEs.

The repository “Expt 2 Script and Data” contains the R analysis script for the Happy/Sad experiment, the RT data, the accuracy data and the two data files (containing the word “graph”) used by ggplot2 to graph the means and SEs.

